gethuman.com 2019-03-19

# Privacy Policy for GetHuman

GetHuman Inc (the "GetHuman," "us," "we" or "our"), the company that operates the GetHuman websites (including but not limited to [gethuman.com](https://gethuman.com/) and [answers.gethuman.com](https://answers.gethuman.com/)) and related site, media or mobile applications (collectively, the "Service"), is serious about protecting your privacy while providing you with a genuine online experience. This Privacy Policy describes:. 

  * Why we collect personal information 
  * What personal information we collect and when it is collected 
  * How your information is used and protected 
  * When and with whom your information is shared 
  * Your choices regarding your personal information 

By using this Service, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy as well as in our Terms of Use. We will post notices of all changes that materially affect the way in which your personally identifiable information may be used or shared in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use the Service after these notices of changes have been posted to the site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control (including any third-party products or services used for logging into the Service or that are integrated with the Service, including our third-party payment processor), or to individuals that we do not employ or manage. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our Service or write to us at: 

    GetHuman, Inc
    800 Boylston Street, Suit 300
    Boston, MA 02199

## Information We Collect

The information we collect from users helps us not only provide the Service but also to personalize and continually improve each user's experience with the Service. Here are the types of information we gather: 

**Information You Give Us**

Registering with us is strictly voluntary, and we do not collect any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") when you do basic searches on the Service. However, registering with us enables you to take advantage of some of our advanced features. When you register with us, we ask you for Personal Information that can be used to contact or identify you, such as your email address. This enables us or the company you are inquiring about to respond to you directly. We will always obtain your express consent before sharing your Personal Information with any such company. 

We may also collect information you supply to us regarding your personal preferences and interests. You can choose not to provide us with any or all of the information we specify or request, but then you may not be able to register with us or to take advantage of some or all of our features. You can register by logging into your account with certain third party social networking sites ("SNS") (including Facebook or Google+) via our Service. If you decide to register with us by logging into a SNS via the Service, we may extract the Personal Information you have provided to the SNS (such as your "real" name, email address and other information you make publicly available via the SNS) from the account you have with such SNS and use that information to register with us; the information we extract may depend on the privacy settings you have with the SNS. 

Once you register with us, you can optionally choose to contribute the following types of publicly viewable information in accordance with our Terms of Use ("Public Information"). Public Information is broadly available to the public, and is accordingly not subject to the protections described in this Privacy Policy. You should only upload Public Information if you are comfortable with these Terms. 

_Public Profile Information_ : When registering or after registering, you can optionally enter in other public profile information such as your name and contact information. 

_Public Content_ : You can create other types of content, such as questions, answers, reviews, ratings, bookmarks and comments, which may be displayed publicly along with associated metadata such as date and time created. 

GetHuman does not knowingly collect Personal Information from minors. If we become aware of the fact that a minor is attempting to submit Personal Information, we will inform the minor that he or she is ineligible to do so. We will then remove this information from our records. If you are the parent/legal guardian of a minor who has given us Personal Information, you may contact us to delete it. 

**Automatic Information and Tracking Tools**

Like many other websites, we and our vendors also collect information through cookies and other automated means. Information of this sort includes: 

_Technical information about your browser and mobile device_ : This information is used in the aggregate to help us optimize the Service for common browsers and devices. 

_Usage information, such as the pages you request, searches you conduct and the features you interact with_ : This behavioral information is collected and used in individualized and aggregate forms to generate statistics about how and by what demographic the Service is being used and to target advertising and communications but is never shared in any form that could be reasonably used to identify you personally. 

_IP address, cookies, tokens and device identifiers_ : These are alphanumeric identifiers that help us to distinguish between unique browsers and devices in order to avoid showing you the same information twice, keep you logged into the Service, prevent duplicate actions, prevent duplicate coupon redemptions and improve your experience. The information we collect from cookies may include your IP address, browser and device characteristics, referring URLs, and a record of your interactions with our Service. Most Web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. We will respect your choices relating to on-line tracking, whether you choose to reject individual cookies or set your web browser to reject cookies and other tracking technology. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, the Service or certain areas or features of the Service. 

Additionally, we may integrate third party services in to our Service in order to personalize your experience. This policy only covers the use of cookies by us. Cookies placed by third party services are governed by the third party terms and privacy policies applicable to those services (which we encourage you to read). For more information about third-party tracking and your choices related to it, please see the Online behavioral advertising (and how to opt out of it) section, below. 

_Crashes and error reports_ : If you encounter a crash or error while using our Service, we may generate a crash report that includes technical, usage and, if you are logged in, your registered Personal Information so that we can diagnose and potentially prevent the problem in the future. 

**Third Party Information**

We may receive information from third parties such as public demographic information to help analyze the use of our services and expand our offering. 

## How We Use the Information We Collect 

**Use**

We use the information we collect for things like: 

  * Responding to inquiries, either directly to you or via our public platform 
  * Marketing and advertising products and services 
  * Conducting research and analysis 
  * Communicating things like promotions and surveys 
  * Identifying you on our Service and tailoring information and offers to you based on your interactions with our Service 
  * Operating, evaluating and improving our business 

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. If you close your account, we may still retain certain information associated with your account for analytical purposes and record keeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, enforce our Terms of Use, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our Service or our users, or take other actions otherwise permitted by law. Further, because of the complexities of the technology involved, we cannot guarantee total or irrevocable deletion of your account information, and we cannot provide you with any specific timelines for deletion. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies. 

## How We Share the Information We Collect 

We do not sell, rent or trade your Personal Information to third parties (unless it is Public Information, as described above). In the normal course of business we shares Personal Information with our agents (such as employees, consultants, service providers and lawyers) to perform tasks on our behalf and may need to share certain information with them in order to provide products or services to you. However, our agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us in providing the service to you as described in this Privacy Policy. We never provide your Personal Information to partners or advertisers, nor do we disclose aggregate information to a partner or advertiser in a manner that would identify you personally. We encourage our service partners to adopt and post privacy policies as well. However, the use of this aggregate information by our service partners, as well as any Personal Information you directly provide to partners or advertisers, is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners and is not subject to our control. 

Sometimes we may be required to share personal information in response to a regulation, court order or subpoena. We may also share information when we believe it's necessary to comply with the law. We also may share information to respond to a government request or when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our customers, or others; to prevent harm or loss; or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity. 

We may also share personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event. 

**Online behavioral advertising (and how to opt out of it)**

We may provide aggregate usage and demographic information to partners and advertisers to help them understand our audience and target their communications accordingly. This information may allow them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge the effectiveness of targeted advertisements. These advertisements may be based on information you submit, or your activities or behaviors on the Service. The information gathered may be used to serve you with advertisements on our Service or on third party websites, including mobile websites or applications. Please see [http://www.youradchoices.com](http://www.youradchoices.com/) or <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> to further understand targeted advertising and your choices about it. Additionally, some third- party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies ([www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)). For more information about tracking and your choices related to it, please see Automatic Information and Tracking Tools section. 

## How We Protect the Information We Collect 

We use reasonable security measures to protect the confidentiality of personal information under our control and appropriately limit access to it. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. 

We use a variety of information security measures to protect your online transactions with us. The Service uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL protects information you submit via our Service such as ordering information including your name, address and credit card number. We will notify you by email if we have reason to believe that your Personal Information has been compromised due to a security breach or used in an unauthorized manner, but by using this Service, you agree to release us from any and all claims arising out of unauthorized use of your information. 

## Your Choices Regarding the Information We Collect 

You may choose to stop receiving marketing or promotional e-mails, direct mail, or other marketing communications, update and correct your personal information, cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, and control when and whether content is posted to third party services, such as Facebook, using both settings provided by us and settings provided by the third party service. 

To do any of these, simply notify us of this decision by following the directions included in any promotional material received from us, or send an email to us at: 

    GetHuman, Inc  
    800 Boylston Street, Suit 300  
    Boston, MA 02199

Please see Automatic Information and Tracking Tools for information about how to reject our use of cookies.   
Please see Online behavioral advertising (and how to opt out of it), for information about how to opt out of online behavioral advertising. 

**Third Party Services and Links to Other Websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites and services, including that of our third party payment processer, many of which have their own privacy policies. Be sure to review the privacy policy on the site you're visiting. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any changes on this page and, if the changes are significant or involve changes to the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by delivering an announcement via our Service or to your email address. If you opt out of communications from us, you may not receive these notifications, but they will still govern your use of the Service and you are responsible for proactively checking for any changes. If you continue to use the Service after changes have been posted, you agree to abide by and be bound by the modified privacy policy. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified by its effective date found at the bottom of this page. 

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this Service, email us at: 

    GetHuman, Inc  
    800 Boylston Street, Suit 300  
    Boston, MA 02199
